<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frontier Digital Ltd on Frontier Digital - Cloud Platform and Devops Professional Services Company</title><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Frontier Digital Ltd on Frontier Digital - Cloud Platform and Devops Professional Services Company</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 21:29:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/epic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/epic/</guid><description>Start Something Epic Our experienced team can work with yours From Base Camp To Summit. We will scale your Cloud Platform using Kubernetes and by expanding to new edge locations, reducing latency.
Base camp Architecural standards RBAC Defined Basic Infrastructure as Code Camp 1 Basic build, test and deploy Basic build, test and deploy Camp 2 Basic developer self service Camp 4 Complex Orchestration mechanism to manage dependencies Summit Full Internal Developer platform</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/featurebox1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/featurebox1/</guid><description>Already using Cloud Software? If you are already on the cloud, but aren’t quite content with your systems, we can help re-structure your cloud to ensure it is actually doing what you need it to do. We can review your infrastructure to help you utilising as much as you can for the best cost. Let’s get your staff trained up on how to make the most of automation and the other features your software provides.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/featurebox2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/featurebox2/</guid><description>Superior Security Cybersecurity is (or should be!) one of the biggest concerns for every business. Our cloud software protects against unauthorised access and enables you to easily limit access to files and folders on a ‘need to know’ basis.
The security stands up to cyber threats and doesn’t rely on your staff to review and update security protocols. This includes much higher change of data recovery should you loose data, when compared with on premise systems.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/featurebox3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/featurebox3/</guid><description>DevOps Orchestration Managing dependencies for applications down to the infrastructure level can be tiresome; Frontier Digital focus on solutions to maintain a full layered environment. When you need more than automation, we implement orchestration that reduces production issues and speed up time to market.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/hero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/hero/</guid><description>We are a boutique Cloud Platform Engineering company. Our experienced team can work with yours.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/section1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/section1/</guid><description>DevOps for the Digital Frontier A hard working Cloud platform is the strong foundation that gives you the capabilities to tackle the challenges that come with being a succesful business. Growing your company is a an adventure; but it’s more akin a long distance trek that a day of Skydiving. For long term success, you need software that grows and adapts to your changing requirements - you get bigger, it gets smarter.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/section2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/section2/</guid><description>Frontier Digital are a bespoke Cloud based and DevOps systems software developer, integrator and coach. That last part, is the most important. For everything system we develop, we make sure that the end user understands how to use it. When you work with Frontier Digital, your team becomes more efficient as they learn how to streamline and improve administrative and operational tasks, giving them more time to focus on what you really hired them to do.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/section3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/section3/</guid><description>Cloud Based Automation So how do you know when it’s time to leap into the cloud? One of the big indicators, is feeling bogged down in too many manual processes. Emailing multiple versions of a document to different colleagues; waiting for your files upload to the CRM; manually adding new email to your contact list…. This can take up hours every week, and that’s time you don’t have to spare if you when you have big plans for the future.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/whyfd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontier-digital.co.uk/index/whyfd/</guid><description>Why Frontier Digital? We guarantee a low MTTR (mean time to recovery when problems arise) Guard against unexpected bills through FinOps We are with you throughout your journey, supporting your growth Approachable, friendly team We make sure you are actually using everything you pay for</description></item></channel></rss>