<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frontier Digital - a Cloud Platform Engineering company on</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/</link><description>Recent content in Frontier Digital - a Cloud Platform Engineering company on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frontierdigital.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Autoscaling Kuberenetes workloads with custom schedules</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/autoscaling-kubernetes-workloads/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/autoscaling-kubernetes-workloads/</guid><description>Autoscaling Kuberenetes workloads with custom schedules Context Would you like to know how we cut annual cloud costs by over 45% for one of our major financial services clients? Read on!
Following on from a previous blog post where we discovered how to make use of custom schedules in ADO pipelines, we decided to use the same mechanism as part of our FinOps practices for one of our major clients.</description></item><item><title>The misconception of simplicity</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/misconception-simplicity/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/misconception-simplicity/</guid><description>Cloud platforms are increasing in popularity, is the current perception correct?</description></item><item><title>Azure DevOps Pipelines with multiple schedules</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/azure-devops-pipelines-with-multiple-schedules/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/azure-devops-pipelines-with-multiple-schedules/</guid><description>Azure DevOps Pipelines with multiple schedules Context A client is aware that significant cost savings could be realised by a scheduled manipulation of some of their deployed resources and services. Their working week leads to predictable hot and cold periods in the utilisation of their build services and pre-production environments in which scaling up and down could take place.
The resources in question don&amp;rsquo;t have any other suitable means to scale based on demand.</description></item><item><title>Why Frontier Digital?</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/why-frontier-digital/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/why-frontier-digital/</guid><description>It’s time for your business to move to the Cloud, but how do you ensure you get there safely, securely and without it running away with the pennies?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/about/better/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/about/better/</guid><description>We’re better. Here’s why&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;We were born out of the realisation that companies moving to the cloud often find their pathway blocked, or spend more time than they expect trying to navigate the system. We want to use our experience to change the way cloud platform is approached, developed and operated.&amp;rdquo;
Craig Anderson, CEO
&amp;ldquo;At Frontier we are not afraid to tackle problems head on. We take time to understand the problem you want to solve and use our experience to engineer a solution with you.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/about/title/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/about/title/</guid><description>About us We are a Cloud Platform Engineering company. We advocate best practices underpinned by a ‘code first’ approach to building and operating cloud platforms.
We have a wide range of expertise in all areas of cloud computing and automation and have delivered automated, secure, observable and cost-effective cloud platforms all over the world.
We believe the best way to effect technology change is by delivering incremental value following agile methodologies, with short feedback loops and focus on continuous improvement.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/epic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/epic/</guid><description>Start something epic Our experienced team can work with yours along any part of your cloud maturity journey from Base Camp to Summit.
Base Camp: Architectural standards, compliance policies and access control model defined Camp 1: Automated Infrastructure as Code deploy CI/CD pipelines running Camp 2: Automated application build, test and deploy CI/CD pipelines running Camp 3: SAST, software supply chain security and FinOps tooling integrated into CI/CD pipelines Camp 4: Advanced single source of truth deployment mechanism to manage and promote between environments running Summit: Full internal developer platform available</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox1/</guid><description>Built for purpose We take time to understand the problem you&amp;rsquo;re trying to solve and use our experience to engineer a solution with you.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox2/</guid><description>Ready to scale We build platforms that take advantage of cloud native capabilities to scale up and down as your applications require.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox3/</guid><description>Automated from the ground up We advocate best practices underpinned by a ‘code first’ approach to building and operating cloud platforms.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/hero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/hero/</guid><description>We are a Cloud Platform Engineering company Our experienced team can work with yours to build automated, secure, observable and cost-effective cloud platforms to all levels of the cloud maturity model.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section1/</guid><description>Start your ascent Moving to the cloud is an adventure but it’s more akin to a long distance trek than a day of skydiving. With a strong foundation - automation, security, observability and cost management - your cloud platform can deliver value at regular milestones. We can help you start your ascent.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section2/</guid><description>Lay a path A mature platform should enable self-service for developers, engineers and other platform consumers. An Internal Developer Platform can help you to guide and standardise your engineering teams on design, implementation and operation of applications running on your platform. We can help you lay a path.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section3/</guid><description>Help others follow safely Engineering teams need fast and regular feedback to ensure the applications they&amp;rsquo;re building are safe, secure and meet the standards you&amp;rsquo;ve set for your platform. Integrating industry-trusted tools into DevOps processes - &amp;ldquo;shifting left&amp;rdquo; - is key to that. We can help you help others follow safely.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/whyfd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/whyfd/</guid><description>Why Frontier Digital? We have a wide range of expertise in all areas of cloud computing and automation and have delivered automated, secure, observable and cost-effective cloud platforms all over the world. We believe in using the right tool for the job, whether it&amp;rsquo;s open source, off the shelf or something more bespoke. We are passionate about delivering incremental value following agile methodologies, with short feedback loops and a focus on continuous improvement.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/architecture/</guid><description>Architecture We design and build scalable platforms so that as you grow, your cloud platform grows with you. Building your platform is just the start; ensuring the platform continues to meet the demands of your accelerating business is what we really excel in. Whether you started out with us or already have a platform in place but have encountered growing pains along the way, Frontier Digital can guide you through the technology required to expand your business efficiently.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_migration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_migration/</guid><description>Cloud Migration It can be challenging to migrate applications from on-premises environments (e.g. a server in your office) to the cloud. Our team of experts have years of experience in cloud migrations and can help you migrate any workload into the cloud safely, securely and on budget.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_security/</guid><description>Cloud Security All code in your platform will be scanned and analysed by a modern security scanning toolchain to ensure the code is secure before it is shipped. Code running in production will be continuously monitored for vulnerabilities and software currency, i.e. we make sure you are always up to date to get the best protection possible.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_tools/</guid><description>Cloud Tools We work with tools that match the capabilities of you and your team. We can recommend the best tools to manage your platform and coach your team in how to use them. The tools we work with include Microsoft Azure, AWS, Google Cloud, Terraform, Ansible, Pulumi, GitHub, Rackspace and DigitalOcean, but we can work with any software system, ensuring that the software stack works for you.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/devops_sysadmin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/devops_sysadmin/</guid><description>DevOps and Sys Admin We are a team of skilled engineers who believe in creating systems that elevate your business to the next level. We keep the code as the source of truth, automate the business logic and make sure documentation is self-generating and up to date. What this means, in practice, is that all of your digital assets and information are stored in once place, which everyone can access. This increases productivity while decreasing frustrations and mistakes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/finops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/finops/</guid><description>FinOps The FinOps model supports you in expanding your cloud with minimal cost. We can audit your processes and find improvements in process, cost, or complexity. Using tooling to continuously manage security and cost of the platform ensures that there are no billing surprises. FinOps gives the different departments within your organisation information on their spending in a way they can easily understand and helps them communicate with each other on the best solution for the whole company.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/landing_zone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/landing_zone/</guid><description>Landing Zone Connectivity and shared services are the beginning of any cloud journey. Our team can get you securely connected to the cloud with a solid foundation from which to start your cloud journey. A Landing Zone enables you to automate many of the processes required to grow your cloud system and gives you a central place to manage your platform.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/mlops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/mlops/</guid><description>MLOps Are you embarking on a machine learning or data engineering project in the cloud? It can be daunting to think about where to start, given the array of tools available. Our experience can help you plan a secure solution and our software and pipeline expertise will ensure that the solution is sustainable, recoverable and grows as easily as your processes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/observability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/observability/</guid><description>Observability We operate and run your chosen cloud platform. This includes day-to-day monitoring and alerting and responding to those alerts and ensuring that the platform runs smoothly, pre-empting downtime and ensuring minimal business disruption.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/readiness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/readiness/</guid><description>Readiness Assessment Are you thinking about adopting one of the cloud providers but are not sure where to start? We can analyse your current setup and advise on a plan that fits your needs. Get in touch for a no-obligation initial chat.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/terms/terms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/terms/terms/</guid><description>Standard Terms and Conditions 1 DEFINITIONS AND INTERPRETATION The following definitions and rules of interpretation apply in these Conditions.
1.1 Definitions: “Business Day” means a day, other than a Saturday or Sunday, when banks in Edinburgh are open for business;
“Charges” means the charges payable by the Customer for the supply of the Services in accordance with Clause 5;
“Commencement Date” means the date on which the Contract comes into existence in accordance with Clauses 2.</description></item></channel></rss>