<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frontier Digital - Cloud Platform and Devops Professional Services Company</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/</link><description>Recent content on Frontier Digital - Cloud Platform and Devops Professional Services Company</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frontierdigital.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Frontier Digital?</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/why-frontier-digital/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/why-frontier-digital/</guid><description>It’s time for your business to get onto the Cloud, but how do you ensure you implement it correctly?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/about/better/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/about/better/</guid><description>We’re Better. Here’s Why… We were born out of the realisation that companies moving to the Cloud had often found their pathway blocked, or were spending more than they expected trying to navigate the system. We want to use our experience to change the way software is developed; your developers should play a key role in your organisation’s journey to achieve your vision and break new ground.
Our goal is that every employee can use the software in a way that makes their job easier and more efficient.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/about/title/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/about/title/</guid><description>About us We are a boutique Cloud Platform Engineering professional services company.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/epic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/epic/</guid><description>Start Something Epic Our experienced team can work with yours From Base Camp To Summit. We will scale your Cloud Platform using Kubernetes and by expanding to new edge locations, reducing latency.
Base camp Architectural standards Access control defined Camp 1 Basic Infrastructure as Code Camp 2 Basic build, test and deploy Camp 3 Basic developer self service Camp 4 Complex Orchestration mechanism to manage dependencies Summit Full Internal Developer platform</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox1/</guid><description>Already using Cloud Software? If you are already on the cloud, but aren’t quite content with your systems, we can help re-structure your cloud to ensure it is actually doing what you need it to do. We can review your infrastructure to help you efficiently utilise as much as you can, and for the best cost. Let’s get your staff trained up on how to make the most of automation and the other features your software provides.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox2/</guid><description>Superior Security Cybersecurity is (or should be!) one of the biggest concerns for every business. Our cloud software protects against unauthorised access and enables you to easily limit access to files and folders on a ‘need to know’ basis.
The security stands up to cyber threats and doesn’t rely on your staff to review and update security protocols. This includes a much higher chance of data recovery should you lose data, when compared with on premise systems.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox3/</guid><description>DevOps Orchestration Managing dependencies for applications down to the infrastructure level can be tiresome; Frontier Digital focus on solutions to maintain a full layered environment. When you need more than automation, we implement orchestration that reduces production issues and speed up time to market.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/hero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/hero/</guid><description>We are a boutique Cloud Platform Engineering company. Our experienced team can work with yours.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section1/</guid><description>DevOps for the Digital Frontier A hard working Cloud platform is the strong foundation that gives you the capabilities to tackle the challenges that come with being a successful business. Growing your company is an adventure; but it’s more akin a long distance trek that a day of Skydiving. For long term success you need software that grows and adapts to your changing requirements - you get bigger, it gets smarter.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section2/</guid><description>Frontier Digital are a bespoke Cloud based and DevOps systems software developer, integrator and coach. And that last part is the most important: For every system we develop we make sure that the end user understands how to use it. When you work with Frontier Digital your team becomes more efficient as they learn how to streamline and improve administrative and operational tasks, giving them more time to focus on what you really hired them to do.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section3/</guid><description>Cloud Based Automation So how do you know when it’s time to leap into the cloud? One of the big indicators is feeling bogged down in too many manual processes. Emailing multiple versions of a document to different colleagues; waiting for your files to upload to the CRM; manually adding new email to your contact list…. This can take up hours every week, and that’s time you don’t have to spare if you when you have big plans for the future.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/whyfd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/whyfd/</guid><description>Why Frontier Digital? We guarantee a low MTTR (mean time to recovery when problems arise) Guard against unexpected bills through FinOps We are with you throughout your journey, supporting your growth Approachable, friendly team We make sure you are actually using everything you pay for</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/architecture/</guid><description>Architecture We design and build scalable platforms so that as you grow, your cloud platform grows with you. Building your platform is just the start; ensuring the platform continues to meet the demands of your accelerating business is what we really excel in. Whether you started out with us or already have a platform in place but have encountered growing pains along the way, Frontier Digital can guide you through the technology required to expand your business efficiently.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_migration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_migration/</guid><description>Cloud Migration It can be challenging to migrate applications from on-premises environments (e.g. a server in your office) to the cloud. Our team of experts have years of experience in cloud migrations and can help you migrate any workload into the cloud safely, securely and on budget.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_security/</guid><description>Cloud Security All code in your platform will be scanned and analysed by a modern security scanning toolchain to ensure the code is secure before it is shipped. Code running in production will be continuously monitored for vulnerabilities and software currency, i.e. we make sure you are always up to date to get the best protection possible.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_tools/</guid><description>Cloud Tools We work with tools that match the capabilities of you and your team. We can recommend the best tools to manage your platform and coach your team in how to use them. The tools we work with include Microsoft Azure, AWS, Google Cloud, Terraform, Ansible, Pulumi, GitHub, Rackspace and DigitalOcean, but we can work with any software system, ensuring that the software stack works for you.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/devops_sysadmin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/devops_sysadmin/</guid><description>DevOps and Sys Admin We are a team of skilled engineers who believe in creating systems that elevate your business to the next level. We keep the code as the source of truth, automate the business logic and make sure documentation is self-generating and up to date. What this means, in practice, is that all of your digital assets and information are stored in once place, which everyone can access. This increases productivity while decreasing frustrations and mistakes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/finops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/finops/</guid><description>FinOps The FinOps model supports you in expanding your cloud with minimal cost. We can audit your processes and find improvements in process, cost, or complexity. Using tooling to continuously manage security and cost of the platform ensures that there are no billing surprises. FinOps gives the different departments within your organisation information on their spending in a way they can easily understand and helps them communicate with each other on the best solution for the whole company.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/landing_zone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/landing_zone/</guid><description>Landing Zone Connectivity and shared services are the beginning of any cloud journey. Our team can get you securely connected to the cloud with a solid foundation from which to start your cloud journey. A Landing Zone enables you to automate many of the processes required to grow your cloud system and gives you a central place to manage your platform.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/mlops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/mlops/</guid><description>MLOps Are you embarking on a machine learning or data engineering project in the cloud? It can be daunting to think about where to start, given the array of tools available. Our experience can help you plan a secure solution and our software and pipeline expertise will ensure that the solution is sustainable, recoverable and grows as easily as your processes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/observability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/observability/</guid><description>Observability We operate and run your chosen cloud platform. This includes day-to-day monitoring and alerting and responding to those alerts and ensuring that the platform runs smoothly, pre-empting downtime and ensuring minimal business disruption.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/readiness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/readiness/</guid><description>Readiness Assessment Are you thinking about adopting one of the cloud providers but are not sure where to start? We can analyse your current setup and advise on a plan that fits your needs. Get in touch for a no-obligation initial chat.</description></item></channel></rss>