<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homes on</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/</link><description>Recent content in Homes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://frontierdigital.net/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/epic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/epic/</guid><description>Start something epic Our experienced team can work with yours along any part of your cloud maturity journey from Base Camp to Summit.
Base Camp: Architectural standards, compliance policies and access control model defined Camp 1: Automated Infrastructure as Code deploy CI/CD pipelines running Camp 2: Automated application build, test and deploy CI/CD pipelines running Camp 3: SAST, software supply chain security and FinOps tooling integrated into CI/CD pipelines Camp 4: Advanced single source of truth deployment mechanism to manage and promote between environments running Summit: Full internal developer platform available</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox1/</guid><description>Built for purpose We take time to understand the problem you&amp;rsquo;re trying to solve and use our experience to engineer a solution with you.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox2/</guid><description>Ready to scale We build platforms that take advantage of cloud native capabilities to scale up and down as your applications require.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/featurebox3/</guid><description>Automated from the ground up We advocate best practices underpinned by a ‘code first’ approach to building and operating cloud platforms.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/hero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/hero/</guid><description>We are a Cloud Platform Engineering company Our experienced team can work with yours to build automated, secure, observable and cost-effective cloud platforms to all levels of the cloud maturity model.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section1/</guid><description>Start your ascent Moving to the cloud is an adventure but it’s more akin to a long distance trek than a day of skydiving. With a strong foundation - automation, security, observability and cost management - your cloud platform can deliver value at regular milestones. We can help you start your ascent.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section2/</guid><description>Lay a path A mature platform should enable self-service for developers, engineers and other platform consumers. An Internal Developer Platform can help you to guide and standardise your engineering teams on design, implementation and operation of applications running on your platform. We can help you lay a path.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/section3/</guid><description>Help others follow safely Engineering teams need fast and regular feedback to ensure the applications they&amp;rsquo;re building are safe, secure and meet the standards you&amp;rsquo;ve set for your platform. Integrating industry-trusted tools into DevOps processes - &amp;ldquo;shifting left&amp;rdquo; - is key to that. We can help you help others follow safely.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/home/whyfd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/home/whyfd/</guid><description>Why Frontier Digital? We have a wide range of expertise in all areas of cloud computing and automation and have delivered automated, secure, observable and cost-effective cloud platforms all over the world. We believe in using the right tool for the job, whether it&amp;rsquo;s open source, off the shelf or something more bespoke. We are passionate about delivering incremental value, with short feedback loops and a focus on continuous improvement. We have security at the front of our minds, partnering with industry experts to ensure that the platforms we build and operate are secure - and stay that way.</description></item></channel></rss>