<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Automation on</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/tags/automation/</link><description>Recent content in Automation on</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frontierdigital.net/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Secrets as code with Mozilla SOPS</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/secrets-as-code/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/secrets-as-code/</guid><description>Secrets as code with Mozilla SOPS The problem Modern cloud platforms move at speed. The rate of change required to stay competitive in any market requires development teams to ship new features at a high velocity. When releasing new features rapidly, it is often difficult to maintain and control the configuration and secrets that are required to make your application work. Part of this problem has been solved by moving configuration to code repositories therefore leveraging all of the advantages of git.</description></item><item><title>Autoscaling Kuberenetes workloads with custom schedules</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/autoscaling-kubernetes-workloads/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/autoscaling-kubernetes-workloads/</guid><description>Autoscaling Kuberenetes workloads with custom schedules Context Would you like to know how we cut annual cloud costs by over 45% for one of our major financial services clients? Read on!
Following on from a previous blog post where we discovered how to make use of custom schedules in ADO pipelines, we decided to use the same mechanism as part of our FinOps practices for one of our major clients.</description></item><item><title>Azure DevOps Pipelines with multiple schedules</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/azure-devops-pipelines-with-multiple-schedules/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/blog/azure-devops-pipelines-with-multiple-schedules/</guid><description>Azure DevOps Pipelines with multiple schedules Context A client is aware that significant cost savings could be realised by a scheduled manipulation of some of their deployed resources and services. Their working week leads to predictable hot and cold periods in the utilisation of their build services and pre-production environments in which scaling up and down could take place.
The resources in question don&amp;rsquo;t have any other suitable means to scale based on demand.</description></item></channel></rss>