<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on Frontier Digital - Cloud Platform and Devops Professional Services Company</title><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on Frontier Digital - Cloud Platform and Devops Professional Services Company</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 21:29:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://frontierdigital.net/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/architecture/</guid><description>Architecture We design and build scalable platforms so that as you grow, your cloud platform grows with you. Building your platform is just the start; ensuring the platform continues to meet the demands of your accelerating business is what we really excel in. Whether you started out with us or already have a platform in place but have encountered growing pains along the way, Frontier Digital can guide you through the technology required to expand your business efficiently.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_migration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_migration/</guid><description>Cloud Migration It can be challenging to migrate applications from on-premises environments (e.g. a server in your office) to the cloud. Our team of experts have years of experience in cloud migrations and can help you migrate any workload into the cloud safely, securely and on budget.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_security/</guid><description>Cloud Security All code in your platform will be scanned and analysed by a modern security scanning toolchain to ensure the code is secure before it is shipped. Code running in production will be continuously monitored for vulnerabilities and software currency, i.e. we make sure you are always up to date to get the best protection possible.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_tools/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/cloud_tools/</guid><description>Cloud Tools We work with tools that match the capabilities of you and your team. We can recommend the best tools to manage your platform and coach your team in how to use them. The tools we work with include Microsoft Azure, AWS, Google Cloud, Terraform, Ansible, Pulumi, GitHub, Rackspace and DigitalOcean, but we can work with any software system, ensuring that the software stack works for you.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/devops_sysadmin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/devops_sysadmin/</guid><description>DevOps and Sys Admin We are a team of skilled engineers who believe in creating systems that elevate your business to the next level. We keep the code as the source of truth, automate the business logic and make sure documentation is self-generating and up to date. What this means, in practice, is that all of your digital assets and information are stored in once place, which everyone can access. This increases productivity while decreasing frustrations and mistakes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/finops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/finops/</guid><description>FinOps The FinOps model supports you in expanding your cloud with minimal cost. We can audit your processes and find improvements in process, cost, or complexity. Using tooling to continuously manage security and cost of the platform ensures that there are no billing surprises. FinOps gives the different departments within your organisation information on their spending in a way they can easily understand and helps them communicate with each other on the best solution for the whole company.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/landing_zone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/landing_zone/</guid><description>Landing Zone Connectivity and shared services are the beginning of any cloud journey. Our team can get you securely connected to the cloud with a solid foundation from which to start your cloud journey. A Landing Zone enables you to automate many of the processes required to grow your cloud system and gives you a central place to manage your platform.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/mlops/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/mlops/</guid><description>MLOps Are you embarking on a machine learning or data engineering project in the cloud? It can be daunting to think about where to start, given the array of tools available. Our experience can help you plan a secure solution and our software and pipeline expertise will ensure that the solution is sustainable, recoverable and grows as easily as your processes.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/observability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/observability/</guid><description>Observability We operate and run your chosen cloud platform. This includes day-to-day monitoring and alerting and responding to those alerts and ensuring that the platform runs smoothly, pre-empting downtime and ensuring minimal business disruption.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://frontierdigital.net/services/readiness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://frontierdigital.net/services/readiness/</guid><description>Readiness Assessment Are you thinking about adopting one of the cloud providers but are not sure where to start? We can analyse your current setup and advise on a plan that fits your needs. Get in touch for a no-obligation initial chat.</description></item></channel></rss>